Mss.B.F113 Mss.B.F113 Mss.B.F113
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Letter to Jean Fabbroni, Florence, B F113; 9x7-1/4; Penrose, Tho[ma]s
    New College, [Oxford], A.L.S. 2p.and add. (see Fabroni papers.) Tells him prices of certain items and suggests he find an agent to purchase them for him.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 9x7-1/2; Penrose, Tho[ma]s
    New College,[Oxford], A.L.S. 2p. (see Fabroni papers.) Has received anatomical preparations and all are pleased with them.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Fabbroni, Florence, Dec. 5, 1803; B F113; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Penrose, Thomas
    Oxford, A.L.S. 3p.and add. (see Fabroni papers.) Wishes to order a wax model for anatomy classes of the human nervous system of the head and neck.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], April 13, 1792; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Perini, Giulio, 1726-1792.
    A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning election to an historical society.
  - Letter to Giuseppe Pelli, Jan. 2, 1784; B F113; 11-3/4x8-1/2; Perini, Giulio, 1726-1792.
    L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Notifies him of election to the Royal Academy of Florence.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabroni, B F113; 9-1/2x8; Petrini, Pietro, 1785-1822.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Forwards correspondence from Cioni to Pacchini, concerning an experiment.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni]., B F113; 7x4-1/2; Pignotti, [Lorenzo], 1739-1812.
    A.L.in 3rd.P. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Invitation to dinner.
  - Letter to Jean Fabbroni, B F113; 10x7-3/4; Pignotti, [Lorenzo], 1739-1812.
    A.L.in 3rd.P. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Congratulates him on his achievements.
  - Letter to Giuseppe Pelli, Florence, Aug. 22, 1799; B F113; 9-1/2x7; Pignotti, L[orenzo], 1739-1812.
    [Answered:] A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Hopes they can visit while at a lake. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Giuseppe Pelli, Florence, Sept. 16, [1799?]; B F113; 9-1/2x7; Pignotti, L[orenzo], 1739-1812.
    A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Refers to Fabroni. Concerning business with Vienna.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 10x8; Pignotti, Lorenzo, 1739-1812.
    A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Thanks for publication. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Giovanni], Fabroni, Dec. 13, 1778; B F113; 6-1/4x4; Planta, [Joseph?], 1744-1827.
    D.in 3rd.P. 1p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Invitation to dinner.
  - Letter to [Abbé Felice] Fontana, B F113; 7-1/4x4-1/2; Planta, [Joseph?], 1744-1827.
    Samedi matin [Saturday morning]. L.in 3rd.P. 1p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Asks him to see if Fabroni can locate a certain publication. Concerning the borrowing of another item.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Florence, Oct. 29, 1814; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Portal, [Antoine de Gaillac], 1742-1832.
    Paris, A.L.S. 4p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his appointment to the mint. Chemistry.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, May 3, 1805; B F113; 9-1/4x7; Portal, [Antoine de Gaillac],1742-1832.
    A.L.S. 3p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) News of Paris.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabroni, Florence, Aug. 1, 1803; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Pozzetti, Pompilio
    Modena, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Asks about law on monies.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Sept. 6, 1779; B F113; 9x7-1/4; Priestley, J[oseph], 1733-1804.
    Calne, A.L.S. 4p. (see Fabroni papers.) Experiments on air, leading to oxygen.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Oct. 17, 1779; B F113; 9x7-1/4; Priestley, J[oseph], 1733-1804.
    Calne, A.L.S. 3p.and add. (see Fabroni papers.) Wishes they could visit together before he leaves England. Refers to experiments on air. Refers to Vaughan and Ingenhousz.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Dec. 23, 1806; B F113; 9x7-1/4; Prony, [Gaspard Clair François Marie] de, 1755-1839.
    Chaffagio, A.L.S. 3p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Lost his luggage and asks Fabroni to try to find it and ship it to him. Remarks on Fossombroni.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, July 25, [1796]; B F113; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Prony, [Gaspard Clair François Marie], 1755-1839.
    4 Thermidor an 7 A.L.S. 1p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Will send his publication to Fossombroni as soon as possible.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabroni, July 10, 1797; B F113; 9-1/2x7; Puccini, T[ommaso], 1749-1811.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Invitation to dinner.
  - Letter to Jean Fabroni, Florence, Oct. 14, 1803; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Quadri, Gio[vanni] Batt[ista]
    Rome, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Will send journals, if possible. Refers to Humboldt.
  - Letter to Jean Fabbroni [Giovanni Fabroni], Paris, Dec. 23, 1809; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Current events. Refers to Cuvier.
  - Letter to Jean Fabbroni [Giovanni Fabroni], Paris, Jan. 12, 1810; B F113; 10x8; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his new post which was offered him. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Oct. 5, 1811; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Various scientists, including Billi. Empire news, in Italy.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabbroni, Rome, Oct. 11, 1811; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Publications. Concerning amounts he has already paid.
  - Letter to Giovanni [Fabroni], Jan. 9, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Coinage of money. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Giovanni [Fabroni], Feb. 8, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Botanical subjects.
  - Letter to Giovanni [Fabroni], Feb. 26, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) News of mutual acquaintinaces in Florence.
  - Letter to Giovanni [Fabroni], May 10, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning sibuet. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Giovanni [Fabroni], Sept. 31, 1812; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 4p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Personal news. Trees.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Paris, July 26, 1813; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Glad his son has been saved. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni, Florence, Oct. 27, 1814; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a manuscript.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Aug. 11, 1817; B F113; 10x8-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Livorno, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Projected travelling.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Aug. 31, 1817; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) His voyage as far as Gibralter.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Nov. 13, 1817; B F113; 12x8; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Rio de Janiero, A.L.S. 5p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers. Concerning his travels to Rio de Janiero, and comments on them.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Aug. 20, 1818; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his sailing to Rio de Janiero.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Nov. 22, 1811; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business. Death of Signora Teresa. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Nov. 29, 1811; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business. Medical news. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Dec. 7, 1811; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business. Received package. Concerning Giovanni Fabroni. Botany.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Dec. 23, 1811; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 4p.,add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Botany. Oaks. Scientific news of Italy.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Dec. 28, 1811; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) News of friends. Business. Friendly letter.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Jan. 18, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business. Botany.
  - Letter to Leopoldo [Fabroni], Jan. 30, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 4p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Botany. Oaks.
  - Letter to Leopold[o] Fabbroni, Feb.13, 1812; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Botanical subjects.
  - Letter to Leopoldo [Fabroni], Feb. 22, 1812; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Botanical subjects. Refers to his father.
  - Letter to Leopoldo [Fabroni], Feb. 29, 1812; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning Georges(?) Sibuet and his Library.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Sept. 10, 1813; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Happy they are coming back. Business.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Sept. 18, 1813; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 3p.and add.,end. (see Fabroni papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Fabbroni [sic], Paris, Oct. 10, 1813; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Florence, A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli-Fabbroni [sic], Florence, July 19, 1828; B F113; 12x8-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Genoa, A.L.S. 1p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning the distribution of his work on South America.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, July 29, 1828; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 3p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Expects to leave France for Africa for natural history studies. Refers to Champolion and De Candolle.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, Aug. 6, 1828; B F113; 8x5; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Archaeology in Sicily. Refers to Champollion.
  - Letter to [Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni], Aug. 26, 1828; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Alexandria, Egypt, A.L.S. 4p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Is in Egypt. Concerning his voyage Refers to champollion.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, Nov. 21, 1828; B F113; 10x8-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 1p.,end.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his travels in the Mediterranean and his study of natural history there.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, Sept. 24, 1828; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/4; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Cairo, A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Trip to Upper Egypt. Description of trip from Alexandria to Cairo.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, Feb. 10, 1829; B F113; 10x8; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    A.L.S. 3p.,end.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his expedition to Nubia.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabroni, Florence, June 9, 1829; B F113; 10x8; Raddi, Giuseppe, 1770-1829.
    Rosetta, Egypt, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Lists letters he has written and says that he has notes used in writing them. Concerning his voyages.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni, Aug. 9, 1819; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Raddi, Luisa
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabbroni, Jan. 30, 1824; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/4; Raddi, Luisa
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning the Raddi family and Giuseppe Raddi.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni]., B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Rainoldi, [Gaetano
    A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a publication.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Valentino Mattia Fabroni], Jan. 21, 1789; B F113; 9-1/4x7-1/4; Raspe, R[odolphe] E[ric], 1737-1794.
    London, A.L.S. 2p.and end. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his publication on natural history in the duke's collection,and other collections in Italy.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Oct. 11, 1798; B F113; 10x7; Re, Filippo, 1763-1817.
    Reggio, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Forwards publication on agriculture.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Bat[tista] Redi, Aug. 5, 1690; B F113; 10-1/2x7-1/2; Redi, Fran[ces]co, 1626-1697.
    Florence, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a book.
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Florence, April 20, [1799]; B F113; 12-1/4x9; Reinhard, [Charles Frédéric, comte], 1761-1837.
    1 Floreal an 7. L.S. 1p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Wishes him bon voyage and hopes the results of his trip will be good.
  - Letter to the minister of the interior, Sept. 15, [1798]; B F113; 9-1/4x7; Reinhard, [Charles Frédéric, comte], 1761-1837.
    Florence,29 Fruitidor an 6 L. 1p. Copy. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Introduces Fabroni, who joins the commission on weights and measures.
  - Statement concerning Giovanni Fabroni, April 19, [1799]; B F113; 9-3/4x8; Reinhard, [Charles Frédéric, comte], 1761-1837.
    Florence, 30 Germinal an 7. D.S. 1p. Copy. In French. (see Fabroni papers)
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Florence, Aug. 5, 1822; B F113; 9-1/2x8; Rennie, George, 1791-1866.
    A.L.S. 3p.and add. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning machinery for minting money.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli-Fabroni, Oct. 3, 1828; B F113; 8-1/2x5; Repetti, Em[anuele], 1776-1852.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian.. (see Fabroni papers.) Business of the geographic society.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli-Fabbroni, June 9, 1833; B F113; 8-1/2x5; Repetti, Eman[uele], 1776-1852.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a report made to the geographical society.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli-Fabbroni, Sept. 16, 1828; B F113; 8-1/2x8; Repetti, Emanuele, 1776-1852.
    Florence, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Notifies him of a meeting of the society.
  - Letter to Leopoldo [Pelli] Fabroni, Sept. 20, 1849; B F113; 10x7; Repetti, Emanuele, 1776-1852.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a publication by Adamo Fabroni.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli-Fabbroni, June 12, 1833; B F113; 12-1/2x8-1/2; Repetti,Em[anuele], 1776-1852.
    A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Has presented the item to the duke.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Fabroni, Florence, July 28, 1803; B F113; 9x7-1/2; Rosini, [Giovanni], 1776-1855.
    Pisa, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Forwards letter from Lando.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Fabroni, Florence, April 16, 1806; B F113; 9-1/2x7-3/4; Rosini, Gio[vanni], 1776-1855.
    Pisa, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Forwards medals.
  - Receipt to Leopoldo Fabbroni, Oct. 26, 1804; B F113; 4-3/4x7; Rosse, Federigo del
    A.D.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, March 12, 1800; B F113; 7-1/4x4-1/2; Ruffo, [Fabrizio], 1744-1827.
    L.in 3rd.P. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Invitation to visit.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], March 5, 1812; B F113; 8x6; Rumford, [Marie Anne Pierette Paulze] Lavoisier, [contesse], 1758-1836.
    A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Forwards letters.
  - Autograph., B F113; 7-1/2x4-1/2; Russell, J[ohn, 6th Duke of Bedford?,] 1766-1839.
    D.S. 1p. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to [Giovanni] Fabroni, Florence, May 28, 1785; B F113; 8-1/2x6-1/2; Sabbathier, [François], 1735-1807.
    Chaulons-sur-Marne, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Thanks for being made a member of the Florentine geographical society.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], March 22, 1797; B F113; 9x6-1/2; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    A.L.S. 2p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) News of events. Refers to Aldini.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Jan. 17, 1800; B F113; 11-1/4x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, July 30, 1800; B F113; 10x7-1/4; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Refers to Banks and to John Adams.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Aug. 12, 1800; B F113; 11-1/2x7-1/2; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Refers to Fontana.
  - Letter to Gio[vanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Dec. (?) 18, 1800; B F113; 11x7; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Refers to Banks.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Aug. 22, [1801]; B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    4 Fruitidoro anno ix A.L.S. 3p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Vaccination.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Sept. 1, [1801]; B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Bologna, 24 Fructidoro anno ix A.L.S. 3p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Vaccination.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Sept. 25, 1801; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Bologna, A.L.S. 2p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Nov. 4, [1801]; B F113; 11-1/2x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, 13 Brum. an x A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Refers to Aldini.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Nov. 11, [1802]; B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, 20 Brumale anno x. A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Scientific experiments.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 9-1/2x6-3/4; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    A.L.S. 2p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 8-1/4x5-1/2; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Bologna, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian, (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 12x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
    Milan, A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 11-3/4x8; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni]., B F113; 9x7-1/2; Sacco, Luigi, 1769-1836.
  - Certificate that Leopoldo Fabroni has studied chemistry under him, 15 July, 1799; B F113; 8x6-1/4; Sage, [Balthazar Geoges], 1740-1824.
    Paris, A.D.S. 1p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.)
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 7-1/4x6; Saint-Non, Abbé [Jean Claude Richard] de, 1727-1791.
    Basil, A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Glad he feels better. Refers to Thomas Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], B F113; 8x6-1/2; Saint-Non, Abbé [Jean Claude Richard] de, 1727-1791.
    A.L.S. 2p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Delighted with his Italian translation of his work.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabroni, B F113; 10x7-1/4; Savi, G[aetano], 1769-1844.
    Florence. A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Introduces Giuli, who comes to visit Tuscany.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabroni, Florence, March 19, 1798; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Savi, Gaetano, 1769-1844.
    Pisa, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his publication. Would like for Sir Joseph Banks to have a copy.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], April 6, 1787; B F113; 10x7; Scarpa, A[ntonio], 1747-1832.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 1p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Business.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, May 1, 1796; B F113; 10x7-1/2; Scarpa, Antonio, 1747-1832.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 1p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning a copy of his book. Refers to Fontana. Will travel to Florence upon the first vacancy in the Royal Museum.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, Aug. 18, 1805; B F113; 9-1/2x7; Scarpa, Antonio, 1747-1832.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning his book on aneurism.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, May 16, 1806; B F113; 9-1/2 7-1/4; Scarpa, Antonio, 1747-1832.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning Brunati and a publication.
  - Letter to Giovanni Fabbroni [sic], Florence, June 23, 1806; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/4; Scarpa, Antonio, 1747-1832.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Concerning Brunati.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], July 10, 1805; B F113; 9-1/4x7-1/2; Scheel, P
    Copenhagen, A.L.S. 4p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Experiments on salt. Chemistry. Medicine.
  - Letter to Jean [Giovanni] Fabbroni [sic], Florence, July 10, 1805; B F113; 9-1/4x7-1/2; Scheel, P
    Copenhagen, A.L.S. 1p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Introduces Heuer, a Danish artist and forwards his publication on medieval archives.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabrony], Dec. 30, 1807; B F113; 9-1/2x7-1/2; Schreiber,
    Pesey, A.L.S. 3p. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Is pleased that Vargas introduces them and thanks Fabroni for his memoirs.
  - Letter to Jean Fabroni, Florence., B F113; 9-1/2x7; Schubart, Barone de
    A.L.S. 1p.and add. In French. (see Fabroni papers.) Tells him the princess will see him, and names the hour.
  - Letter to Leopoldo Pelli Fabbroni [sic] Florence, May 29, 1835; B F113; 10-1/2x8-1/2; Scopoli, G A
    Verona, A.L.S. 1p.and add.,end. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Friendly letter.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Jan. 1, 1787; B F113; 11-1/2x8; Scopoli, Gio[vanni] Anto[nio], 1723-1788.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 3p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Difficulties with Spallanzani who accused him of thieving from the museum of natural history.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], March 16, 1787; B F113; 11-3/4x7-3/4; Scopoli, Gio[vanni] Anto[nio], 1723-1788.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 2p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Chemical experiments.
  - Letter to [Giovanni Fabroni], Aug. 3, 1788; B F113; 10x7; Scopoli, Gio[vanni] Anto[nio], 1723-1788.
    Pavia, A.L.S. 3p. In Italian. (see Fabroni papers.) Chemical news, especially experiments for agriculture and on phlogiston.
  - Letter to Giov[anni] Fabroni, Florence, July 5, 1807; B F113; 9-3/4x7-1/2; Sismondi, J[ean] C[harles] Léonard] Simonde de, 1773-1852.